synotrip.com 2007-06-23

# About_Us - privacy policy | Synotrip.com

Guide

﻿  \- [The Synotrip Team](http://www.synotrip.com/about-us/the-synotrip-team/)  
  \- [Join Synotrip](http://www.synotrip.com/about-us/join-synotrip/)  
  \- [Our Partners](http://www.synotrip.com/about-us/partners/)  
  \- [Advertise on Synotrip](http://www.synotrip.com/about-us/advertise/)  
  \- [Link to Us](http://www.synotrip.com/about-us/link-to-us/)  
  \- [Contact Us](http://www.synotrip.com/about-us/contact-us/) | 

| 

#### Synotrip Privacy Policy  
  
---  
  
Synotrip.com understands the importance of protecting its users’ privacy. 

**A) _When and why we collect personal informatio_ n:**

**Browsing Synotrip.com** does not result in any personally identifiable information being collected. However, we may collect statistics including IP address, time of day, date and browser type. This information is used to make improvements to our site.

**Cookies on Synotrip.com** collect information about your computer. A "cookie" is a small data file that is automatically stored by your browser. Cookies don’t offer any personally identifiable information. Cookies can be turned on or off in your browser’s preferences.

Third-party advertisers that Synotrip.com is associated with may also use cookies to collect information. 

**Registration on Synotrip.com** involves providing your email address as well as other personal information that you may or may not include. This information may be displayed on Synotrip.com.

**B) _Consent_**

Synotrip.com assumes that you consent to the collection and use of your information as outlined in section A.

**C) _Questions_**

For questions or complaints about the Synotrip.com Privacy Policy please feel free to contact us.  
  
|
